Many as four projected top 10 picks in
this draft. Have you seen that happen
before where one school had that kind of
concentration of of talent? Yeah, I
don't know the history part of that, but
I think uh
this place has been producing guys at a
really high level and uh what's really
impressive is you get to know these
players, they're excellent people, high
character, they're really good football
players, and they're really prepared to
go in the NFL. When you have contact
with these guys previously, I'm sure you
guys are contacting them already. What
more is gleaned from a day like today? I
think it's as much exposure as you can,
just getting to know these guys in
different settings. And so obviously we
get to see the football part on film,
but really getting to know the people in
and out of these days.
What makes these Ohio State guys so NFL
ready because the Saints have benefited
from it through the years? Many NFL
teams have. Yeah, I I think again, it's
the preparation these guys put in to
this program. They are very well
prepared. They've been coached really,
really well. And um they're ready for
the lifestyle of the NFL. You guys have
taken care of a lot of areas in free
agency. How flexible does that allow you
to be in this draft? I think that's
always the goal to address as many
things as we want to address. We know
it's a long process through the whole
off season going all the way through
training camp and the preseason. But uh
the more uh opportunities we have to add
really good players with really with
really good people on top of it, uh
we'll keep doing that and obviously the
draft will be the next big process. You
know, so after this, what's on the
docket for the Saints? You guys go back
home and start conducting the um 101s
there or
Yeah, we'll finish up some of this. A
lot of our staff is out this this week
uh just going to as many different spots
as we possibly can to get as much
exposure. And then next week uh we'll
get back in there. We'll start uh kind
of going through the process of the
draft meetings and the readings and
putting the board put together. You
know, you've heard a lot of well,
several free agents join the team and
say, "You know what? We joined this team
because we like the way it's heading,
especially at quarterback." How does
that make you feel, I guess, especially
when guys notice what you're doing at
quarterback?
Yeah, obviously I I thought Tyler
finished off the the season well. And so
uh yeah, I think we got a good
foundation laid. Uh we got a lot of uh
really really good players that are
coming up, you know, a nice blend of
some guys who've got a lot of experience
in our league with some young guys. And
so it's it's all about continuing to
develop and grow together and we'll be
in a good place. All right, thank you.
All right, thank you.